let questions = [
    {
        question: 'Who is the player with the most world cups?',
        options: [
            'Pelé',
            'Garrincha',
            'Cafú',
            'Maradona'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },

    {
        question: 'Who is the player with the most goals in world cups?',
        options: [
            'Pelé',
            'Messi',
            'Klose',
            'Ronaldo fenômeno'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },

    {
        question: 'Which club has the most Champions League?',
        options: [
            'Barcelona',
            'Real Madrid',
            'Milan',
            'Bayern Munich'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },

    {
        question: 'What club does messi currently play for?',
        options: [
            'Barcelona',
            'Al-Nassr',
            'PSG',
            'Argentina'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the Brazilian player with the most titles?',
        options: [
            'Daniel Alves',
            'Neymar',
            'Ronaldinho Gaúcho',
            'Pelé'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },

    {
        question: 'What country is Arsenal from?',
        options: [
            'Spain',
            'Germany',
            'USA',
            'England'
        ],
        answer: 3
    },

    {
        question: 'Currently, who is the player with the highest salary in football?',
        options: [
            'Messi',
            'Cristiano Ronaldo',
            'Mbappe',
            'Neymar'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },

    {
        question: 'Which team won the 2018 world cup?',
        options: [
            'France',
            'Argentina',
            'Germany',
            'Italy'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },

    {
        question: 'Which of these clubs is not a spanish club?',
        options: [
            'Barcelona',
            'Girona',
            'Schalke 04',
            'Villarreal'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },

    {
        question: 'Which player has the most goals of free-kicks?',
        options: [
            'Zico',
            'Ronaldinho Gaúcho',
            'Marcos Assunção',
            'Beckham'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
]